本字幕仅作学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业用途 否则后果自负
==GA字幕组==
翻译：入江之鲸 冰糖 一生为白 飞行猪 开心的小末
校对：流年打死不表白 关注海燕的毯子 lynhoo00 没抢到东西的蓉小张 K在苦逼找事做 伽尘师太
字幕特效/时间轴：闹不闹得住菇 无限Boss爱渣  压制：米兰伯爵
好了 Ducky 我搞定了
All right, Ducky, I'm done.
谢谢你 Tim
Thank you, Tim.
可怜的姑娘
You poor dear.
可能根本就没听到车来的声音
Probably didn't even hear it coming.
嘿 Tony在哪儿
Hey, where's Tony?
我不知道
I don't know.
我说我可以载他一程
I offered to give him a lift,
但他说会有人来接他
but he said someone would pick him up.
从华盛顿到匡蒂科吗
From DC to Quantico?
我听着也觉得奇怪
Sounded strange to me, too.
我真不知道 没有车他怎么活
I don't know how he's surviving without a car.
是他吗
Is that him?
不 是Delilah
No. It's Delilah.
我们在计划着如何忙里偷闲度过一个美好的周末
We're talking about sneaking away for a long weekend.
不错嘛
Nice.
你们两个小女生要是聊完了
If you hens are finished,
就过来帮我个忙
I could do with some help.
噢 好的
Oh, yes.
她是海军陆战队下士 名叫Jody Ray
Her name's Petty Officer Third Class Jody Ray.
巡逻队员在日出后发现了她的尸体
Patrol spotted her body just after sunrise.
她在海军基地诊所工作
She works at the base clinic.
昨晚九点打卡下班
Punched out just after 21:00 last night.
然后她跑着回去吗
And she went for a run?
同事说她在为马拉松做准备
Coworker said she was training for a marathon.
过去的几个月里她几乎每晚都跑步
Had been running almost every night for the past few months.
通知近亲了吗?
Next of kin been notified?
伤亡援助电话处正在处理 先生
CACO team is on it, sir.
好的 谢谢
All right, thanks.
很高兴你加入我们 DiNozzo
Nice of you to join us, DiNozzo.
抱歉 来迟了
Yeah, sorry.
嗨 Jimmy
Hey, Jimmy.
所以我错过了什么
So, what did I miss?
谁开车送你过来的
Who was it that drove you all the way over here?
噢
Oh.
一个朋友
A friend.
认真点儿
No, seriously.
我是认真的
Seriously.
我该干什么 拍照吗
What should I do, photograph?
不 我已经拍过了
No, I already did it.
呃 好吧
Egh. All right.
Duck
Duck?
昨晚
Last night, 22:00 hours,
十点左右
or thereabouts.
嗨 Abbs
Hey, Abbs.
有什么发现
Come up with anything?
有进展
Making progress.
你看
Look, okay, this is a part
这是这辆车车头灯装置的一部分
of the vehicle's headlight assembly.
它的制造商和型号是什么
What's the make and model?
在美国
There are 47 manufacturers
有47家小汽车和货车的制造商
of cars and trucks in the United States.
每家生产的汽车 型号和外形都多种多样
Each one of those produces multiple models and body styles.
并且零件和外包装每隔几年就会被重新设计
And the parts and the trim are redesigned every few years.
因此有无限种可能
There are zillions of possibilities.
为什么每个人都假定
Why would anyone assume that I could take
我能通过这小小的一块塑料
a teeny, tiny piece of plastic
就能轻易识别出它属于哪种车
and easily identify a vehicle?
它的制造商和型号是什么
What's the make and model?
一辆2003到2005年生产的Dodge牌敞篷载货卡车
A 2003 to a 2005 Dodge Ram pickup truck.
非常感谢你
Thank you very much.
但是我们不得不把范围缩小
But we're going to have to narrow it down.
那个基地每天都停着数百辆货车
There's hundreds of trucks on that base every day.
这就是你打断我时我正在做的事
That's what I was doing when you interrupted me.
是这样的 Ray下士手表上残留着微量的
So, there was a trace of the vehicle's paint
货车油漆
on Petty Officer Ray's watch.
这是我们的颜色选项
These are our color choices.
在最顶层我们得到了胺吸磷红
On the top we have Inferno Red.
在底层我们得到了深莫尔滕红
And the bottom we have Deep Molten Red.
我不知道谁想出了这些名字
I don't know who comes up with these names.
你怎么认为的
What do you think?
我想我会选上面的
I'm going to have to go with the top one.
同意
Agreed.
胺吸磷红在2005到2008年才有
So Inferno Red was only available between 2005 and 2008.
因此前灯玻璃和这种颜色的油漆有交集的唯一一年
So the only year in common between the headlight lens
是在2005年
and the color is 2005.
因此我们正在寻找一辆红色的2005年制造的Dodge牌敞篷载货卡车
Ergo we are looking for a red 2005 Dodge Ram pickup truck.
Abby 你是最棒的
Abby, you are the best.
这是理所当然的
Still taken for granted.
只是因为我才让它变得简单 并不意味着它原本简单
Just 'cause I make it look easy doesn't mean it is.
为什么你怀疑上士Justin Dunne
Why do you suspect Staff Sergeant Justin Dunne?
Abby研究了肇事逃逸车辆的
Abby I.D.'d the make, model and color
型号和颜色
of the hit-and-run vehicle.
在基地注册的车里只有一辆符合条件 它属于 Dunne
Only one registered on base and it belongs to Dunne.
我检查了门卫的摄像头画面
I checked the gate security footage.
他的货车昨晚根本没有离开过匡蒂科
His truck never left Quantico last night.
我们知道他的哪些信息 单身
What do we know about him? Single.
高中一毕业就入伍了
Joined the Corps right out of high school.
他是个直升机机械师
He's a helo mechanic.
本周晚些时候将被部署到
Scheduled to deploy on an LHA
去往地中海的两栖攻击舰服役
to the Med, later this week.
还有最相关的
And most pertinent...
他有过酒驾史
he has a DUI in his past.
把他带进来
Bring him in.
我很高兴一切进展得这么快
I love it when it all comes together so quickly.
我不这么认为 反而会很担心
Not me. Makes me nervous.
这也太简单了
Too easy.
走吧
Let's go.
你没想过要买辆新车吗
You ever going to get a new car?
第一 我从来不买新车
Well, firstly, I never buy new cars.
第二我需要能点燃我的激情的东西
Secondly, I need something that ignites my passions.
它就像女人
It's like a woman.
在我做出承诺前我要爱上它
I need to be in love before I commit.
你从来没对女人做出过承诺
You've never committed to a woman.
Dunne上士 我们是海军罪案调查处
Sergeant Dunne. NCIS.
Dunne上士
Sergeant Dunne!
别动 海军罪案调查处
Freeze. NCIS.
是 这是我的货车 但是
Yeah, that's my truck, but
我发誓 我不知道它怎么会跑那去了
I swear, I don't know how it got that way.
你昨晚没开它吗 没有
You didn't drive it last night? No.
我已经好几天没用过那辆车了
I haven't used the truck in a couple of days.
那你怎么去上班 我步行去 就当是锻炼
How do you get to work? I walk. Need the exercise.
维修处所在的海湾离我的住处并不远
The maintenance bay isn't that far from my quarters.
昨晚十点你在哪
Where were you last night, 22:00 hours?
我在我的房间里...睡觉
I was in my room... asleep.
经历了艰难的一周
Had a tough week.
我精疲力竭
I was exhausted.
你确定你不是因为喝高了
You sure you weren't drunk
而忘记了自己做了些什么吧
and you just don't remember what you did?
我们知道你曾酒驾
We know about your DUI.
我头脑清醒了13个月了
I've been sober for 13 months.
我每周有三到四次会议
I go to three or four meetings a week.
好吧 如果车不是你开的 你是无辜的
So, if you weren't driving the pickup and you're innocent,
为什么你要爬窗户逃走
why were you climbing out a window?
我知道我的权利
I know my rights.
在我的律师来之前我什么也不会说的
I'm not saying any more until I have a lawyer.
好得
Okay.
接下来你可以自己选一个律师了
Then you can have the lawyer of your choice
或者军法处长给你指派一个
or JAG will assign one to you.
嗨 McGee
Hey, McGee.
Dunne上士的右脚上的靴子你带过来了吗
Did you bring me Sergeant Dunne's right boot?
抱歉 Abbs 他请了律师 限制了我们的调查
Sorry, Abbs, he lawyered up and didn't give a permissive search.
好吧 那你有没有好好看一看他的右脚
Hmm. Well, did you get a good look at his feet?
啊 犯罪现场留下的脚印
Huh? Well, the footprint that you cast
那是海军陆战队标准
at the crime scene, it's a standard-issue Marine Corps
战斗靴 尺码是十英寸半
combat boot, size ten and a half.
我猜他可能也穿那个码
Well, I guess he might wear that size.
靴子穿了很久了 在右脚跟
It's well worn and has a very distinctive gash
有一个非常好辨认的切口
in the right heel.
我希望犯罪现场的鞋印能和Dunne上士的靴子相吻合
I'd just really love to match it to Sergeant Dunne.
这样啊 那你就只能等到明天了
Well, you're going to have to wait till morning.
这里有什么发现么
Any luck here?
哦 这绝对是肇事逃逸的那辆货车
Oh, this is definitely the pickup truck.
货车的轮胎符合犯罪现场留下的轮胎印
The tires match the tracks that were in the dirt.
我还在车头找到了头发 血迹和衣服上的纤维
And I got hair, blood and clothing fibers
能和被害人的特征相匹配
off the front end that match our victim.
就这样 我明天就能拿到DNA确认单
So, I'll get DNA confirmation in the morning,
我们现在先把这辆车锁起来
and we should have it locked up.
很好
Great.
对了 自Tony的车撞毁了后
Hey, have you been giving Tony rides to work
你有没有开车送他上班么
since his car was wrecked?
没有
No.
哦
Hmm.
今天早上有人开车
Somebody dropped him off
一路把他送到了匡蒂科
all the way out at Quantico this morning.
莫非他在和某人约会
Is he dating someone?
哦 我不这么想
Oh... I don't think so.
哦
Hmm.
你的味道总是那么好闻
You always smell so great.
我猜你又一次错过了今年的
Let me guess-- you missed the sexual harassment meeting
"防止职场性骚扰"讲座
again this year.
嘿 伙计们 快看我在休息室里发现了谁
Hey, everybody, look who I found in the lobby.
嘿 Clark
Hey, Clark.
-大家好 -早啊 Carrie
- Hey, guys. - Morning, Carrie.
我似乎还没有这个荣幸
I don't think I've had the pleasure.
这位是Mallard医生
Dr. Mallard,
这位是前FBI探员 Carrie Clark
meet former FBI agent Carrie Clark.
现在在私营法律事务所任职
Now in private law practice.
很高兴认识你 医生
Nice to meet you, Doctor.
-我也是 -Carrie在几年前的港务局案中
- Likewise. - Carrie worked
负责诺福克海军基地那边的事务
【注：Norfolk是美国最大的海军基地 绝大部分舰艇都是在这里生产的】
the Norfolk side of the Port Authority case
使Fornell脸上大为增光
a few years ago, made Fornell look good.
这可不是个容易的活儿
It was a tough job.
你们帮了不少忙
No, you guys made it easy.
我不记得那个案子了
I don't remember that case.
是个巨额财产盗窃案 Ducky
Grand theft, Ducky,
没有尸体 无须尸检 所以你没参与
no autopsy, no body, no you.
原来如此
Ah.
是谁把你带到NCIS来的
What brings you to NCIS?
我是来见Dunne上士的
I'm here to see Sergeant Dunne.
你是他的律师
You're his lawyer?
-告诉我这不是真的 -我是 他在哪里
【Say it ain`t so是1988年上映的美国体育电影《八面威风》中的经典台词】
- Say it ain't so. - Yes, where is he?
Dunne上士在院子那端的拘留所里
Staff Sergeant Dunne's in a holding cell across the yard.
McGee探员会带你过去
Agent McGee can take you to him.
多谢
Thank you.
很高兴见到大家
Good to see you guys.
-再见 -Duck
- Bye. - Duck,
你随时可以移交
you can release Petty Officer Ray's body any time
Ray下士的尸体
you're ready.
你注意到Carrie有什么不同了吗 老大
You notice anything different about Carrie, boss?
婚戒不在了
No wedding ring.
跟你说过 她丈夫就是个手提包
Told you the husband was a handbag.
手提包
Handbag?
挎在手臂上的没用的东西
Something useless you hang on your arm.
噢
Oh.
嘿 Fornell探员 我是DiNozzo
Hey, Agent Fornell, it's DiNozzo.
关于那位美丽动人的Carrie Clark
Listen, can you give me the skinny
你能告诉我一些小道消息么
on the ever-fetching Carrie Clark?
你好
Hello.
我是Carrie Clark
I'm Carrie Clark.
没想到你长得这么漂亮
Didn't expect you to look like you do.
有什么问题吗
Is that a problem?
要是你像我表哥说的那么优秀 就没问题
Not if you're as good as my cousin said.
目前还没有任何投诉
Well, I haven't had any complaints.
你即将因为一些非常严重的指控而被提审
You're about to be arraigned on some very serious charges.
关于这个逃逸事件 我什么都不知道
I don't know anything about a hit-and-run.
如果真是我的皮卡车的话 也不是我在驾驶
If it was my pickup, someone else was driving.
你觉得是谁在开车
Any idea who?
Justin 我想要相信你 但你看起来非常不安
Justin, I want to believe you, but you seem very nervous.
有什么想告诉我的吗
Is there something that you want to tell me?
昨晚十点你在哪里
Where were you at 10:00 last night?
有什么关系
Doesn't matter.
当然有关系
Of course it does.
-我有不在场证明 -好
- I have an alibi. - Okay.
你就需要知道这些
That's all you need to know.
你要告诉我吗
Are you going to tell me?
好吧 如果你是这种态度
All right, if that is going to be your attitude,
我来给你省点钱吧
how about I save you some money?
军法署会为你安排一位免费律师
JAG will assign someone to you for free.
等一下
Hold on.
这间屋子可能被监听吗
Could this room be bugged?
不 不会的 那是违法的
No, no way-- that would be illegal.
你在录音我们的谈话吗
Are you recording our conversation?
没有
No.
你是我的律师
You're my lawyer.
无论我说了什么 你都不能告诉任何人 是吗
Anything I say, you can't tell anyone?
这叫做"律师-当事人保密特权"
It's called attorney-client privilege.
你所说的一切 我都会保密
Everything that you say is confidential.
除非你授权 这些谈话不会被泄露
It doesn't leave this room unless you want it to.
职业道德不允许我
Rules of ethics prohibit me
将所讨论的内容告知任何人
from telling anyone what we discuss.
你能保证吗
You sure?
我向你保证 Justin
I promise you, Justin.
那个女孩被杀时
When that girl was killed,
我在35英里外的福尔斯彻奇市
【注：维吉尼亚州的一个城市】
I was 35 miles away in Falls Church.
你在那里做什么
And what were you doing there?
捅死一个人
Stabbing a guy to death.
你干嘛要查看航班时刻表
Why are you checking airline schedules?
迈阿密
Miami?
你必须要知道所有事情吗
Do you have to know everything?
是的 好奇是我的本性
Yes, it's in my DNA.
如果我不告诉你的话 你会把我给逼疯的 所以...
Well, you're gonna drive me crazy until I tell you, so...
这里没什么事情了 案子也快结束了
Things are quiet here, this case is wrapping up.
接下来我会有几天的休假
I've got a few vacation days coming,
Delilah和我商量着
so Delilah and I have been talking
打算离开这里 共度一个长周末
about getting away for a long weekend.
McGee 真让我刮目相看啊
McGee, I'm impressed.
迈阿密 南海滩 酒吧 石头蟹
Miami, South Beach, hot clubs, stone crabs.
真不像你的风格
It is unlike you.
我就知道我不该告诉你
I knew I shouldn't have said anything.
噢
Oh.
没花多长时间啊
That didn't take long.
你的委托人醒悟了吗
Your client come to his senses?
想要坦白吗
Wants to confess?
不
No.
那么是想要做个交易吗
Wants to make a deal, then?
Dunne上士说他是无辜的
Sergeant Dunne says he's innocent.
无辜
Innocent?
我们有证据证明 他的皮卡车与受害人相关联
We've forensically tied his pickup to the victim.
我们去问他问题的时候 他试图逃跑
He ran when we tried to question him.
他声称他有不在场证明
He claims he has an alibi.
那么证明是什么 我们会确认一下
Well, what is it? We'll check it out.
事情没那么简单 Gibbs
Well, it is not that simple, Gibbs,
他是在保密的情况下告诉我的
he told me in confidence.
这是机密信息
It's privileged.
如果他不想自己告诉你的话
If he doesn't want to tell you himself,
我也束手无策
then my hands are tied.
我们有48个小时 来决定是指控他或者释放他
We've got 48 hours to either charge him or let him go.
给我们一些信息
Give us something.
这样吧 我自己去调查他的不在场证明
All right, listen, I will go check out his alibi myself
然后我再来找你
and I will get back to you.
这家伙面对车祸致人死命罪
The guy's facing vehicular homicide
以及肇事逃逸的指控
and hit-and-run charges.
却不肯提供不在场证明
He won't use an alibi?
他疯了吗
Is he crazy?
Abbs
Abbs.
Gibbs 你太了不起了
Gibbs... you're amazing.
你是怎么知道是其他人在开车
How did you know that someone else was driving the truck?
你发现了什么
What'd you find?
是我没发现的那部分更有趣
Well, it's more what I didn't find that's interesting.
在你打电话之前 我只是试图
I mean, before you called, I was just trying
将受害者与车辆联系起来 而且我的确做到了
to match the victim to the vehicle, which I did.
-但是 -但是当你问我
- But? - But then, when you asked me
有没有可能
if there's a chance that someone
是非车主的其他人在驾驶时
other than the owner of the truck was driving,
我在整辆车上搜寻指纹 可是什么都没有找到
I dusted the whole thing for prints, I didn't find any.
-所以只有Dunne上士的指纹吗 -不
- Just Staff Sergeant Dunne's? - No.
我是说 无 没 零 空 啥也没有
I mean, like none, nada, zip, zilch, nothing.
基本上这辆车的整个表面
Almost the entire surface of the truck
都被擦去了指纹的痕迹
was wiped clean of fingerprints--
门把手 方向盘 档位
the door handle, the steering wheel, the gearshift,
座椅调节器 所有地方
the seat adjuster, everything.
这让我想起了我的Horace叔叔
Now, I got reminded o-of my Uncle Horace.
他总是丢三落四的
He was always losing things
比如他的眼镜 钱包 钥匙
like his glasses and his wallet and his keys.
他好几次都被锁在自己的车外
He got locked out of his own car so many times
所以他在车上藏了一把钥匙
that he, he hid a key on his car.
于是我发现了这个
And then I found... this...
就藏在前轮圈下面
...under the front wheel well.
被擦干净了么
Wiped clean?
没错 包括其中的钥匙
Oh, yeah, including the key inside.
车主不可能做出这种事情
That is hardly something that the owner would do.
是其他人在驾驶这辆车
Someone else was driving the truck.
对 而且他们还试图掩盖痕迹
Yes, and they tried to make it look like they weren't.
谢了 Abbs
Thanks, Abbs.
我不理解人为什么要跑
I don't understand why people run.
跑步很有疗效
Oh, well, it's therapeutic,
对心血管问题有极大的益处
it has great cardiovascular benefits.
而且还会刺激内啡肽分泌
【注：又称安多芬 有镇痛及保持快乐的功能】
What's more, it gets the old endorphins pumping.
我跟你说 跑步让我十分兴奋
I'll tell you, running gives me a great high.
我是说那个司机
I was referring to the driver
为什么要从肇事现场逃逸 Palmer先生
running from the scene of the accident, Mr. Palmer.
噢 对 没错
Oh, yes, yes.
你知道吗 这个国家目前涉及行人的肇事逃逸
Did you know that pedestrian hit-and-runs are
比例前所未有之高
at an epidemic rate in this country?
在美国发生的
Nearly 11%
所有交通事故中 有百分之十一
of all traffic accidents in the United States are
是肇事逃逸
hit-and-runs.
那是Ray下士吗
That Petty Officer Ray?
是的
Yes.
把这个尸体留得久一点
Hold on to the body for a little while longer,
可以吗 Duck
will you, Duck?
你签署了尸体移交文件
You signed the release.
有什么变化吗
Has something changed?
是的
Yeah.
但我还不知道是什么
But I don't know what.
喂 我是Gibbs
Yeah, it's Gibbs.
Hi 我是Carrie Clark
Hi, it's Carrie Clark.
好的 Carrie 你查到什么
Yeah, Carrie, what do you got?
是这样的 Dunne的不在场证明
Well, Dunne's alibi
查清楚了 非常可靠
checks out, it's solid.
嗯 告诉我 我不能
Mm-hmm, tell me. I can't.
你们得开始寻找
You're going to have to start looking
真正的逃逸肇事司机 因为他不是我的委托人
for the real hit-and-run driver because it's not my client.
Carrie 听着 我不能仅凭你的话来判断 好吗
Carrie, look, I can't just take your word for it, okay?
告诉我一些线索
Give me something here.
你必须自己解决这事 Gibbs
You're gonna have to figure this one out on your own, Gibbs.
Jethro 出什么问题了吗
Jethro, is something wrong?
看起来你今天终究是不能离开我们了
Looks like you won't be leaving us today after all,
亲爱的
my dear.
McGee,
追踪最后一通电话 可以吗
trace the last call, will you?
你想要我查出是谁打的
You want me to find out who it was from?
是Carrie Clark打的
It was from Carrie Clark.
通常她的名字都会在屏幕上显示出来
Usually her name comes up on that little window there.
但这一次没有 那里只显示了一个数字
This time it didn't; it was just a number.
嗯
Hmm.
她说了什么
What did she say?
说她委托人的不在场证明已经核实
Said her client's alibi checked out.
我不相信
I don't believe it.
好吧 这个数字属于一个投币电话
Well, the number belongs to a pay phone.
投币电话
Pay phone?
我还以为它们都销声匿迹了呢
I didn't think there were any left.
325 金合欢街 福尔斯彻奇市
325 Acacia Avenue in Falls Church.
就在一个图书馆前面
It's in front of the library.
Carrie有手机
Carrie has a cell.
为什么她要用投币电话
Why would she use a pay phone?
不知道
Not sure.
她知道她委托人的不在场证明
She knows her client's alibi.
她也知道她不能告诉我们
She knows she can't tell us.
你认为怎样呢 老大
What are you thinking, boss?
Carrie知道我们会对此感兴趣
Carrie knows we'll be intrigued,
她知道我们会追踪这通电话
she knows that we'll trace the call.
她是不是特地给我们留了条线索
Did she just drop a bread crumb?
是的 去 快过去
Yeah. Go. Go on.
就是那个投币电话
There's the pay phone.
为什么Carrie要从这里打
Why was Carrie calling from here?
图书馆 五金商店
Library, hardware store?
哦 就是那了 性用品商品
Oh, there we go, Great Sexpectations.
我对此深表怀疑 Tony
I seriously doubt it, Tony.
嘿 那里有一辆警察巡逻车
Hey, there's a squad car.
是的 让我们过去问问
Yeah, let's check it out.
你可曾查出Carrie是否离婚了
Did you ever find out if Carrie was divorced?
啊 暂时分居
Ah. Trial separation.
她没有带结婚戒指
She's not wearing her ring.
你知道这代表什么
You know what that means.
这段感情结束了
It's over.
嘿
Hey.
NCIS
NCIS.
特别探员DiNozzo和McGee
Special Agents DiNozzo and McGee.
Dockry 凶案组
Dockry, Homicide.
凶案组
Homicide?
你们来这里干嘛
What are you guys up to?
哦 只是在街头徘徊 枯燥无味
Oh, just pounding the pavement, boring Navy stuff.
是的 不像凶杀案那么严肃认真
Yeah, nothing serious like homicide.
谁死了
Who's dead?
商店的店主――Donny Sullivan
Store owner-- Donny Sullivan.
前天晚上被人刺死
Stabbed to death night before last.
尸体是一个员工昨天早上在楼上的住处发现的
Body was found in the upstairs residence yesterday morning by an employee.
有头绪吗 没有什么具体的
Any leads? Nothing concrete yet.
我能帮你们什么忙吗
Anything I can help you guys with?
哦 不 我们得走了
Ah, no, we got to go.
他很饿了
He gets hungry.
没错 回头见
It's true. See you around.
嘿 你们认识特别探员Gibbs吗?
Hey, do you guys know a Special Agent Gibbs?
哦 是的 我们亲切地称呼他为"老大"
Oh, yeah, we affectionately refer to him as "boss."
告诉他Hickory的儿子向他问好
Tell him Hickory's son said hi.
Hickory
Hickory?
他会明白的
He'll know.
商店店主的谋杀案大致和肇事逃逸发生在同一时间
The storekeeper's murder happened about the same time as the hit-and-run.
你认为这件事情和Dunne的不在场证明有关
Think this has something to do with Dunne's alibi?
如果Dunne参与了这件凶案 那么他是怎么在匡蒂科和这里来回的
If Dunne was involved, then how'd he get from Quantico to here and back?
他的卡车从来没有离开过基地
His truck never left the base.
我觉得你的迈阿密激情周末刚刚跟你说再见了
I think your amorous little weekend in Miami just went bye-bye.
是的 Gibbs 嘿 老大
Yeah. Gibbs. Hey, boss.
我们在Dunne的不在场证明上也许有线索了
We might have a lead on Dunne's alibi.
尽可能查出你能查到的--小心行事 DiNozzo
Find out what you can-- discreetly, DiNozzo.
Gibbs Gibbs Gibbs 如之前我告诉过你的那样我想擦拭
Gibbs, Gibbs, Gibbs, so I told you that I dusted
整辆卡车便于查找指纹 但是我没有
the entire truck for prints, but I didn't.
我只擦了会被触摸的地方
I only dusted the places that a person would touch,
随后我意识到如果有人想要
and then I realized that if someone's going
调整座位的高低 那样的话
to adjust the seat lever, which they did,
也很有可能调整后视镜
they would probably also adjust the rearview mirror.
猜猜我发现了什么--
And guess what I found--
在后视镜的后面采集到一枚新鲜的右手拇指指纹
a fresh right thumbprint on its backside.
拇指指纹有名字吗
Thumbprint have a name?
别傻了 Gibbs
Don't be silly, Gibbs,
拇指指纹怎么可能有名字呢
thumbprints don't have names.
人才有
People do.
我第一时间将它和所有在匡蒂科的人的指纹作对比
My first pass was to run it against all the personnel at Quantico.
于是这便是所有我要做的事情了
And that's all I had to do.
二等兵Daniel Cliff
Private Daniel Cliff.
Gibbs很快就会过来
Gibbs will be in, in a minute.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你知道他们为什么带我来这里吗
You know why they brought me over here?
不知道
No.
我告诉他们除非我律师在场 否则我一句话也不会说
I told them I wouldn't say anything else until my lawyer was present.
是的 我核实过你的不在场证明
Well, I checked your alibi.
你没有撒谎
You weren't lying.
嘿 你不知道玻璃的另一边都有谁
Hey, you don't know who's on the other side of that glass.
咱们就不要再讨论这个问题了
Let's not discuss it again.
你知道所有你需要做的
You know all you have to.
我是无辜的
I'm innocent.
就不能等到早上吗
Couldn't this have waited till the morning?
不能
Nope.
你认识他吗 是的
You know him? Yeah,
二等兵Cliff--我见过他
Private Cliff-- I see him around.
你们俩关系很好
You two close?
不
No.
我们一起出去喝过几次酒
We hung a couple of times back when I was drinking.
那是很久很久以前了
That was a long time ago.
最近你们有见过面吗
Have you seen each other lately?
在洗衣店 娱乐室 见过他 就这些
Run into him in the laundry, rec room, that's it.
你同意让二等兵Cliff
You give Private Cliff permission
开你的小型轻便卡车
to drive your pickup truck?
去你的 当然没有
Hell, no.
这是怎么回事
What was that about?
Gibbs 看来你的肇事逃逸案子已经有了一个嫌疑犯
Gibbs? Sounds like you have a suspect for your hit-and-run.
能让我的委托人离开吗？还不行
You gonna let my client go? Not yet.
拜托 他在这里仅仅是因为配合你们
Come on. He's due to deploy.
还没有把二等兵Cliff带过来问话
Haven't brought Private Cliff in for questioning yet.
好吧 你的48小时时间快到了
Well, your 48-hour clock is ticking.
如果你明天之前还不指控我的委托人
If you don't charge my client by tomorrow,
那你就必须让他走
you have to let him go.
你知道的 一些有趣的事情刚刚发生
You know, a funny thing happened.
我们得到了一个线索
We got a tip.
指引我们去了一家在福尔斯彻奇市的雪茄店
Sent us to a cigar store in Falls Church.
真的吗
Really?
是的 那是个犯罪现场 凶杀案
Yeah, it was a crime scene, a homicide.
如果你的委托人那晚没有在基地开着他的卡车
If your client wasn't driving his truck on base the other night,
那他会不会在福尔斯彻奇市呢
could he have been in Falls Church?
我只关心Dunne上士的权利
My only concern is Sergeant Dunne's rights.
他没有参与这起肇事逃逸案件
He wasn't involved in the hit-and-run.
嗯
Hmm.
非否认的否认
A non-denial denial.
就像Jason Robards在惊天大阴谋里扮演的Ben Bradlee一样
Jason Robards, as Ben Bradlee in All the President's Men.
她没有说"不"
She didn't say "no."
哦 你真是疯了
Oh, you're crazy.
不 你肯定需要眼镜了
No, you must need glasses.
是的是的 好吧 晚点再聊
Yeah, yeah. All right, later.
什么那么好笑
What's so funny?
人力资源部的Hollander
That was Hollander in HR.
她声称今天早上看到你
She claims that she saw you this morning
在一辆公交车的前门下车
at the front gate getting off a city bus.
是的 那是我
Yeah, that was me.
听着 我知道我曾经因为你乘公交车开过你玩笑
Listen, I know I made fun of you in the past for riding the bus,
但我必须承认我错了
but I have to admit I was wrong.
我这段时间一直乘坐公共交通
I've been using public transportation,
而且我真的很喜欢
and I really like it.
你在开玩笑 不
You're kidding. No.
那样我可以有时间去读书
I have time to read,
打一些电话 最重要的是...
make some calls and, best of all...
我可以观察人们
I get to watch people.
人类是如此地令人神魂颠倒
People are fascinating.
好吧 Tony 我...
Okay, Tony, I'm...
就算我不知道我自己现在是什么
I don't even know what I am right now.
但是我懂你 而且我知道这不是你
But I know you, and this is not you.
老大 我检查了Dunne上士的所有电子邮件
Boss, I went through Sergeant Dunne's e-mails,
电话和信用卡
phone calls and credit cards.
什么都没查到
I came up empty.
他和那个死去的雪茄店老板没有任何关系
There's no connecting him to the dead cigar-store owner.
他杀那人的动机是什么
What would his motive be to kill the guy?
但我却发现Dunne给一个马里兰州的电话号码打了很多次
Did find out Dunne exchanged a lot of calls with a Maryland cell phone number.
电话号码属于一个Olivia Chandler的人
Belongs to an Olivia Chandler.
是的 好吧 查出她是谁
Yeah, well, find out who she is.
是的
Yup.
嗯 我们能否大胆运用福尔斯彻奇市警察局的资料库搜索一下Dunne上士的名字
Hmm. Do we dare run Sergeant Dunne's name by Falls Church PD,
也许我们能够找到他们之间的联系
see if they can make a connection?
不能这么做
Can't do that.
我们要保护Carrie Clark
Got to protect Carrie Clark.
你可以暗地里做
You can do it off the record.
那个负责凶杀案的警探似乎认识你
The homicide detective in charge seemed to know you.
谁 额 他说告诉你
Who? Well, he said to tell you,
"Hickory'的儿子向你问好"
"Hickory's son says hello."
那是Paul Dockry
That's Paul Dockry.
Hickory Dickory Dockry
Hickory Dickory Dockry.
他老爸和我在同一个陆战队
His dad and I were in the Corps together.
快来 DiNozzo 你跟着我
Come on, DiNozzo. You're with me.
哈 人类真是令人神魂颠倒
Huh. People are fascinating.
这枚靴子的印记是在犯罪现场找到的
This boot print was found at a crime scene
杀害了一名下士
that killed a petty officer.
你的靴子 跟肇事车辆右轮胎上的抠图吻合
This is the same boot, the same cutout at the right heel.
你知道 我们还掌握了什么吗 Cliff？
And you know what else, Cliff?
我们在卡车后视镜上发现了
We got your thumbprint on the rearview mirror
你的拇指指纹
of that vehicle.
到底发生了什么事情？
What happened?
当时天很黑
It was dark.
等我看到她的时候 一切都晚了
I couldn't see her until it was too late.
你开着Dunne上士的卡车干什么？
What were you doing with Staff Sergeant Dunne's truck?
我喝了几杯
I had a few drinks.
我认识斯塔福德的这个女孩
I know this girl in Stafford.
我无意间听Dunne在录音室提过
I overheard Dunne in the rec room.
他说这星期很累 会早点睡觉
Said he had a rough week and was gonna hit the rack early.
我觉得可以开他的车子
Figured I'd take his truck and be back
在他发现之前 就能赶回来的 屁话
before he even missed it. Bull!
你是怎么知道车子外藏着钥匙？
How'd you know about the hidden key?
大概一年前 他当时还在酗酒
About a year ago, when he was still drinking,
他昏昏沉沉 把自己锁在了车子外边
he got wasted, locked himself out of his truck.
于是他找到藏着的车钥匙 让我送他回家
Got the hidden key out, had me drive him home.
你就眼睁睁 把一个受伤的女性扔在路边等死？
You left an injured woman to die by the side of the road?
不！
No!
我停下车了
I stopped.
我知道她已经死了
I knew she was dead,
然后意识到这一切看起来有多糟
and I realized how bad it all looked.
我当时喝醉了 还开着一辆偷来的车
I was drinking, I was driving a stolen vehicle.
我慌了 然后赶快把车开回停车场
I just panicked and drove back to the parking lot.
你得相信我的话
You got to believe me.
这只是个意外
It was an accident.
我来钉死他 哼
I'll book him. Uh-uh.
如果我们起诉 Private Cliff
If we charge Private Cliff
犯了肇事逃逸罪
with the hit-and-run,
我们就得释放 Dunne上士
we got to let Staff Sergeant Dunne go.
而我并不准备这样做
I'm not ready to do that.
只剩几小时
We only have a few more hours
法定羁押Dunne上士的时间就到了
until the clock runs out on Dunne.
把他关进牢房
Put him in a holding cell.
-你好 Paul
-你好 Gibbs
Hey, Paul. Hey, Gibbs.
抱歉 等我一会
Sorry. Just give me a sec.
我得给女儿发完短信
I got to finish this text to my daughter.
这是她跟我交流的唯一方式
Only way she'll communicate me.
这孩子从来不接电话
The kid never answers her phone.
好久不见
Been a long time.
令尊怎么样了？
How's your dad?
老顽固
Stubborn as always.
我以为会在我妹妹的婚礼上碰到你
Thought I might run into you at my kid sister's wedding.
哦 不 我对婚礼不感冒
Oh, no, no. I'm not... I'm not big on weddings.
我理解
I can understand that.
谢谢你能见我
Thanks for meeting me.
嗯 我在福尔彻奇市碰见了你的探员
Yeah. I ran into your agents in Falls Church.
我断定 那可不是巧合
Taking it, that wasn't a coincidence.
哦 不是吧
Uh, no. So,
你对我的谋杀案有什么兴趣？
what's your interest in my homicide?
呃 说起来复杂了 一团糟
Well, it's complicated, messy.
我们追查线索的时候
Following a lead.
扣押了一个跟罪行无关的人
Holding someone on an unrelated charge.
看似有不在场证明
Seems to have an alibi,
但是他貌似跟你的死亡店主有关系
but he may have been involved with your dead storekeeper
-很乐意跟他聊聊 -现在还不行
Like to talk to him. Can't let you, not yet.
我们还在保护信息来源
Still trying to protect a source.
目前你扣押了他
You have him in custody.
对 目前扣押了他
Yeah, for the time being.
关于你的案子 你能跟我分享点什么？
What can you tell me about your case?
我们发现Sullivan是个赌徒
Discovered Sullivan was a bookie.
用香烟店做幌子
Used the cigar store as a front.
你们羁押的人 看上去是个赌徒？
Guy you holding like to gamble?
我会查明白的
I'll find out.
你们现在有嫌疑人吗？
You got any suspects for the murder?
有...也没有
Yes... and no.
劣迹斑斑的监狱常客 Wendell Kaiser
Loser with a mile-long rap sheet, Wendell Kaiser.
对Sullivan不满已久了
Into Sullivan big-time.
双方公然的争吵过
Very public arguments.
Kaiser甚至威胁过死者
Kaiser even makes threats.
然而 Kaiser有无懈可击的不在场证明
However, airtight alibi.
谋杀案发生的时候 他正在纽约
In New York at the time of the murder.
今天早上才回来 嗯
Just got back this morning. Hmm.
也许现在很流行不在场证明 哈？
Maybe alibis are in season, huh?
好的
Okay.
干酪汉堡
Cheeseburger,
不加配料的炸薯条
no dressing, fries.
我错过什么了？ 你根本没点菜
Did I miss something? You didn't even order.
哦 他不需要开口点菜
Well, he doesn't have to.
谢谢你 Elaine
Thanks, Elaine.
嗯 你能把Kaiser的档案给我吗？
Can you, uh, get me Kaiser's file?
当然可以
Sure.
我会把要点 发到你邮箱
I'll e-mail you the highlights.
你们羁押的那个人 不会碰巧就是受雇的职业杀手吧
Your guy wouldn't happen to be a hit man for hire, would he?
不 我觉得不是
No. I don't think so.
怎么了？ 需要点什么？
What? Need something?
嗯 我需要一把刀来切下汉堡
Yeah, a knife to cut this beast.
不错
That'll work.
不 不 不
No, no, no.
你在开玩笑吧
You're not serious.
她怎么可能嫁给他呢
There's no way she's married to him.
他们结婚差不多5年了
Almost five years.
再次诠释了什么叫做花瓶妻子
The very definition of a trophy wife.
-你在看什么？-Olivia Chandler
What you looking at? Olivia Chandler.
跟Dunne上士
The woman who Sergeant Dunne
发短信 打电话的女人
has been exchanging texts and calls with.
那个糟老头
That little man
肯定非常
must have a big,
-非常有钱 -她嫁给他
big... bank account. She's married to him.
一起住在切维蔡斯村
They live together in Chevy Chase Village.
世界无比精彩
Very la-dee-dah.
她的唯一违规记录是酒后驾车
Only thing on her record is a DUI.
交警发现她的时候 她正开着阿斯顿马丁横冲直撞
She was picked up for driving erratically in her Aston Martin.
太搞笑了
So many jokes.
（她那么有钱 ）肯定开的是阿斯顿丁
Of course she drives an Aston Martin.
当我搜索有没有交通摄像头
When I was searching traffic cameras
拍到谋杀案当晚
to see if I could place Dunne anywhere near the cigar store
Dunne上士在香烟商店附近出现
the night of the murder,
我找到一些有趣的东西
I found something interesting.
我发现了Olivia Chandler的汽车
Olivia Chandler's car.
这张照片是在距离香烟店一个街区的地方拍的
Now, this was taken a block from the cigar store.
由于车窗颜色
Because of the tinted windows,
所以没法确定车里都有谁
you can't make out who's inside.
我把照片发给了Abby
I sent it to Abby.
距离很远 不过她或许能够增强一下图像
It's a long shot, but maybe she can enhance the image.
Sullivan是个赌徒
Sullivan was a bookie.
福尔彻奇市警方有一个嫌疑犯
Falls Church police had a suspect,
但是他有不在场证明
but he has an alibi.
Dockry探长说他会把嫌犯的档案发到我邮箱
Detective Dockry said he was going to e-mail the file.
他已经发了
He did.
Wendell Kaiser McGee
Wendell Kaiser. McGee--
你查一下 Dunne上士有没有赌博的习惯
see if Staff Sergeant Dunne had a gambling problem
或者是跟这个人的任何联系
or any connection to this guy.
DiNozzo...
查一下Olivia Chandler.
check out Olivia Chandler.
很高兴 接受任务
With pleasure.
谢谢你 老大
Thank you, boss.
有什么我能帮你的
May I help you?
噢 我希望你能帮我呢
Oh, I hope so.
NCIS特别探员Anthony DiNozzo
NCIS Special Agent Anthony DiNozzo.
NCIS
NCIS？
我喜欢这辆车 它真火辣
I love this car. It's smoking hot.
我目前在汽车市场里
I'm in the market myself.
我有选择障碍
Between vehicles right now.
名车耗油量大 但是詹姆斯邦德也开这样的车
Terrible gas mileage, but that's what James Bond drives.
（我总觉得Tony在含沙射影说olivia，你们怎么看）
你知道这个事实吗
Did you know that?
我不清楚  你来这干什么
I have no idea. What do you want?
噢 我们在调查一名海军军官
Oh, we're investigating a Marine.
Justin Dunne上士
Staff Sergeant Justin Dunne.
你是怎么认识他的
How do you know him?
-我不认识他 -真的吗？
-I don't. -Really?
你跟他可是打过不少电话
'Cause you exchanged a lot of calls with him,
这就说明你认识他啊
and that would suggest otherwise.
我们在一次匿名戒酒会上认识的
【A.A：Alcoholics Anonymous:匿名戒酒会】
We met at an A.A. meeting.
我们彼此相互支持
We talk to each other for support.
保持清醒是个持久战
Sobriety is an ongoing battle.
那你为什么说不认识他
So why'd you say you didn't know him?
因为 匿名戒酒会的成员对外保持匿名
The second "A" in A.A. is for "anonymous."
我不应该在这谈论他和其他人
I shouldn't be talking about him or anyone else.
明白了
Gotcha.
所以你这是要出门旅行吗
So you're taking a little trip?
我跟几个女性朋友去牙买加
I'm going to Jamaica with some girlfriends.
噢 牙买加
Yeah, mon. Jamaica.
祝你玩得愉快
Well, have yourself a nice time.
你找到Dunne上士和死去的赌徒
Did you connect Staff Sergeant Dunne to the dead bookie
或者和福尔斯彻奇案子嫌疑人的联系了吗
or the Falls Church suspect?
还没有
No, not yet.
根据我问过的人所说的来看
Based on the people I've talked to,
Dunne似乎并不是一个赌徒
it appears that Dunne's not a gambler.
我还得去跟进其它几条线索
I still have other avenues to pursue,
我只是一直没时间把他们全部查完
I just haven't had the time to do it all.
-Tony 你有什么发现 -哦 是的
- Tony, you got something? - Oh, yeah.
你绝对不敢相信Olivia Chandler有多火辣
You won't believe how hot Olivia Chandler is.
真人比照片好看多了
Photos don't do her justice.
她和Dunne上士是什么关系
What's with her and Staff Sergeant Dunne?
她声称她们只是
Well, she claims they're only acquaintances
在A.A.会议上相识的
from A.A. meetings.
但我觉得不仅仅是这样
But I think it's more than that.
你说你有Dunne的信用卡账单--把它放上来
You said you had Dunne's credit card charges-- put them up.
-为什么 -相信我 放上来
-Why? -Trust me, put them up there.
好了 我们在找什么
All right, what are we looking for?
好了 如果真如我所想象的那样
Well, if they're doing what I think they're doing,
他们是不会在她家里做那事的
they're not doing it at her place.
我也不相信一个住在切维蔡斯有钱的家庭主妇
And I don't think a rich housewife from Chevy Chase
会舍得挪动她尊贵的大腿跑去匡提科
is dragging those long legs all the way down to Quantico.
等等 就在这里
Okay, wait. Hold on.
切维蔡斯旅馆
Chevy Chase Lodge.
那里 那里和那里
There, there and there.
三个晚上 或许还有更多
Three nights, probably more.
McGee 撤下来
Take it down, McGee.
48小时的监禁时间到了
Our 48 hours are up.
是的
Yep.
我什么时候能来开走我的车
When do I get my truck back?
我去查一下切维蔡斯旅店
I'm going to check out the Chevy Chase Lodge.
以交通肇事罪逮捕二等兵CLIFF
Book Private Cliff for the hit-and-run.
这件案子结束了 另一个还不知道结果
That's one case closed, another wide open.
是的 亲爱的 我了解
Yes, dear, I understand.
你了解吗
Do you?
-你有认真在听吗 -我听着呢
-Do you even hear? -I hear you.
不 不 不 我永远不会
No, no, no. I-I would never...
好吧...这是你妈妈的主意吗
Well... oh, it's your mother's idea?
是的 是她的意思
Yes, it's my mother's idea!
为什么我对此一点也不惊讶
Why does that not surprise me?
我得挂了 有客人在等我
I have to go. I have a guest waiting.
真的有客人在等我
I do have a guest waiting.
我没有编
I'm not making that up.
额...先生 你能帮助我吗
Uh... could you help me, please, sir?
这是谁 喂
Who is that? Hello?
好的 我一会再打给你
Okay. I'll call you later.
好 我宁愿去地狱也不想再打给你
Fine! Like hell I will.
你结婚了
You married?
噢 没有. 额..
Oh. No. Uh...
我是个联邦探员
I'm a federal agent.
DiNozzo.
有几个问题要问你
Like to ask a few questions.
好吧 联邦探员 尽管问吧
All right, federal agent, ask away.
你见过这个人吗
Have you seen this man?
是的
Yeah.
没错
Yeah, sure.
算是个常客
Sort of a regular.
嗯
Mmm?
那么，他是一个人来还是...
So, does he come alone or...?
他倒是想让我这么认为
Well, he'd like me to think that.
不是 他的朋友从没来过前厅
No, his friend never comes to the lobby.
他停下车 她就直接进房间
He parks the car, and she goes directly to the room.
你自己就会去想 你知道 他们或者结了婚 对吧
So you got to figure, you know, one or both are married, right?
没错 是的
Right. Yeah.
所以你从来没见过她
So you've never seen her?
实际上 我有一次装作
Well, actually, I did the old
敲错了门去看过
knock-on-the-wrong-door routine one time.
她长这样吗？
She look like this?
是的 这就是她
Yeah, that's her.
这样的女人，你是永远不会忘记的
Woman like that, you do not forget.
对吧 我是说 你能想象跟这样一位女士共度一晚...
Right? I mean, can you imagine what one night with...
我发誓 这老太婆绝对有通灵的能力
I swear, the old witch is psychic.
每当我一想起其它的女人
If I have so much as a thought of another woman...
你不必接这个电话
You don't have to answer that.
我必须接 你想
I have to. What...?!
干吗？
...do you want?
我了解了 好运
I got it. Good luck.
你需要..如果..
Just, do you need... if...
拿张名片吧 先生
Take a card, sir.
谢谢
Thank you.
给
Here.
Duck,跟你一起喝酒总是很享受啊
Ah, always enjoy having a drink with you, Duck,
不过，这回不像是听完交响乐回家路过我这这么简单
but this isn't exactly on your way home from the symphony.
你在想什么
What's on your mind?
我正想问你同样的问题 我有些好奇
Well, curiously, I was about to ask you that.
你看起来有些困惑不安
You've seemed... troubled
自从你昨天在验尸房接了那个电话以后
since you took that call in Autopsy yesterday.
你通常都会很好的隐藏自己的感觉
Usually you're a master at hiding your feelings.
这是基于你专业的视角吗
That your professional opinion?
跟一个侧写师一起工作的
The occupational hazard
职业风险
of working with a profiler.
嗯..
Mmm.
我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
有点担心Carrie Clark
A little concerned about Carrie Clark.
律师 是的 她很不错
The lawyer? Yeah, she's good.
她帮助她的代理人免于起诉
She got her client released without being charged.
我察觉到你下一句 有个"但是"
I sense a "but."
她很有良心和道德感
Well, she does have a conscience.
这是件好事 不是吗
Well, that's a good thing, isn't it?
我们了解到一些关于她的代理人的事情
We learned some things about her client
她或多或少指引我们去的
that she may or may not have led us to.
秘密的资料
Privileged information?
医生 我必须很小心的处理这件事情
Doc, I got to be careful how I handle this.
保护Carrie
For Carrie's sake.
不然她会被取消律师资格
She could get disbarred.
我知道你 Jethro
Well, I know you, Jethro.
听起来她像在做正确的事 你也是
It sounds as if she's doing the right thing, as you are.
音乐会怎么样
So how was the concert?
非常好 柴可夫斯基第二号交响乐
Great. Tchaikovsky's Second.
我从来不知道他还给电影配过音乐
I never realized that he wrote music for the movies.
这是我非常迷恋的车
That's a car I've always had the hots for.
也许那才是我该开的
Maybe that's what I should get.
太老土了
It's too old.
你不能开那样的车
You can't drive a car like that.
这不实用
It's not practical.
这就是你的问题 麦古板
That's the problem with you, McGeezer.
所有的事都以实用为先
Everything has to be practical.
我...
What...
我的意思是 我从未见你
What I mean is, I've never known you
做出一点出格的事
to do anything even a little risqué.
Tony 你根本不知道我闲暇时在干什么
Tony, you have no idea what I do on my time off.
确实如此 我不知道
You know, that's true, I don't.
你为什么不跟我说呢
Why don't you tell me?
分享下喽  来啊  说啊
Share. Rock me. Sock me.
看  那是Wendell Kaiser
Well, there's Wendell Kaiser.
猜猜如果福尔斯彻奇的警察也在跟踪他
Wonder if Falls Church PD is tailing him, too.
Kaiser是他们的嫌犯
Kaiser's their suspect.
Kaiser准备去教堂
Is Kaiser going to church?
不 是一个AA聚会
【注：Alcoholics Anonymous，戒酒互助社】
No. It's an A.A. meeting.
他们每天早上都在这个时间见面
They meet here every morning at this time.
等等 你怎么知道的
Wait, how do you know that?
Anthony
Anthony!
你在这儿干嘛呢
What are you doing here?
你的聚会应该在晚上啊
Your meeting's not until tonight.
Reverend Miller 我... - 带了个新成员吗
Reverend Miller, I, uh... - Bringing a new member?
呃...
Um...
他正在考虑要不要加入呢  有点疑神疑鬼
He's thinking about it. A little gun-shy.
McGee  这是牧师
McGee, the Rev.
加入我们吧
Please join us.
这是个非常安全的地方
It's a very safe place.
随时欢迎你
All are welcome.
Tony  怎么回事
Tony, what's going on?
你酗酒了吗
Do you have a drinking problem?
不 不 我只是...
No. No, I just...
我加入了这个人的互助小组
I joined this men's support group.
每周两晚在教堂大厅聚会
Meets in the church hall two nights a week.
认真的
You serious?
嗯
Mm-hmm.
我知道 这...
I know, it...
听起来并不像我 但是...
it doesn't sound like me, but...
过去这些年 我只是...
with the past year, I just...
只是想振作一下
wanted to shake things up a little bit.
结识一些新的朋友
Meet some new people.
在健身房 他告诉了我这个组织
This guy at the gym told me about the group,
我觉得听起来还不错
and I thought it sounded like a good idea.
觉得...很有趣
And it... it is, it's fun.
有一天早上 牧师带我去了匡迪科
The Rev drove me to Quantico the other morning.
真是个有意思的人
Interesting guy.
他帮我缓解评头论足的坏毛病
He's helping me be less judgmental.
你知道的 Kaiser一会就要来了
You know, Kaiser's going to be here for a while.
我们得回去
We should get back.
Dunne上士 Olivia Chandler以及Wendell Kaiser
Sergeant Dunne, Olivia Chandler and Wendell Kaiser
都有一个共同点
all have one thing in common.
他们都参加AA聚会
They all go to A.A. meetings.
他们也许是在那认识的
That's probably where they met.
上士和花瓶妻子是情人关系
The sergeant and the trophy wife are lovers.
Chevy Chase旅馆的前台说
The desk clerk at the Chevy Chase Lodge
他们都是常客
said that they were regulars.
就像那部电影《体热》里的
【体热：赫特是佛罗里达的职业律师，遇上了已婚的社交名媛特纳，与之热恋
并共同密谋杀害她富有的丈夫】
It's just like that movie Body Heat.
威廉姆・赫特和凯瑟琳・特纳
William Hurt and Kathleen Turner.
天呐 老大 她确实有问题啊
God, she was really something, boss.
出乎意料
A head turner.
但我觉得有点离谱
But I digress.
不管怎么讲 他们是年轻的恋人 就像这俩人
Anyway, they were young lovers, just like these two,
还图谋富豪丈夫的钱财
and they wanted the rich husband's money
他们需要除掉那个富豪
and him out of the way.
另一方面 Wendell Kaiser
On the other hand, you've got
输了很大笔钱给他的赌马经纪人
Wendell Kaiser, who's deep in debt to his bookie
他需要除掉那个经纪人
and needs him off his back.
所以他们互相帮助对方杀掉了想杀的人
So they help each other out and switch murders.
当Kaiser在纽约时
While Kaiser was in New York,
Dunne在Olivia的帮助下杀了赌马经纪人
Dunne killed the bookie with Olivia's help.
她负责开车  她的车就在附近
She drove him. Her car was in the vicinity.
谁又会怀疑他们呢
Who would ever suspect them?
我是说 根本没有联系也没有动机
I mean, there's no connection, no motive.
第二天Dunne上士开始部署行动
Tomorrow Sergeant Dunne is going to deploy
而Olivia Chandler去了牙买加
and Olivia Chandler is off to Jamaica.
我打赌当他们离开时
And I'm betting that while they're away,
她的丈夫将会遭遇
her husband's going to have a terrible accident
一起由Kaiser先生策划的严重事故
at the hands of Mr. Kaiser here,
一个跟他完全没关系的人
a man with whom he has no connection.
两起谋杀案 三个确凿的不在场证明
Two murders, three solid alibis.
真是个有趣的解释
Interesting theory.
我们知道这是个很难证明的阴谋
We know it's going to be a hard conspiracy for us to prove.
我们都要仔细些  不仅仅是案件
We got to be careful-- it's not our case.
有一个办法
There's a way.
去找一些细微的联系
Find the weak link.
嗨 Kaiser
Hey, Kaiser.
你有时间吗
You got a minute?
Dockry警探
Detective Dockry.
我认为我们之间没什么可说的了
I thought we were done.
我把我知道的关于Sullivan的所有事都告诉你了
Look, I told you everything I know about Sullivan.
是的 但是呢 又有一些新情况
Yeah, well, something's come up.
我们去警局吧 聊聊新的情况
Let's go to the station. We can talk about it.
呃 我哪也不去
Nah, I'm not going anywhere.
听着 我跟Sullivan的谋杀案一点关系都没有
Look, I had nothing to do with Sullivan's murder.
我当时在纽约 亲 你可以查的
I was in New York, man. You checked it out.
你真的想在你朋友面前被带走吗
You really want to do this in front of your friends?
我哪也不跟你去
I'm not going anywhere with you.
我们了解你的兄弟 Dunne上士
We know about your buddy, Sergeant Dunne,
还有他的女朋友
and his girlfriend.
那就让我来解释下案件是怎么进行的
So let me explain how this works.
首先 两方嫌疑人互通情报达成共识
First suspect to flip on the others gets the deal.
Olivia Chandler
Olivia Chandler?
嗨 Gibbs
Hey, Gibbs.
DiNozzo告诉我如果你不在家
DiNozzo told me that if you weren't at home
我没准能在这找到你
I would probably find you here.
坐吧
Have a seat.
有什么问题吗
There a problem?
没有 我...
No, I...
只是听到一个福尔斯彻奇的警察
just heard that Falls Church PD
逮捕了我的前委托人 Dunne上士
arrested my former client, Sergeant Dunne.
是吗
Really?
他们对他有多项指控
Yeah, they booked him on multiple charges,
包括串通谋杀和杀死一人
including conspiracy to commit murder and murder one.
他们是怎么抓到他的
How'd they get him?
很显然是他的其中一个同谋者
Apparently one of his coconspirators
将证据交给了警方
turned state's evidence.
有时候...你挺走运的
Sometimes... you get lucky.
这就是走运
Mmm, is that what it was?
他们拿到了搜查令
They got a warrant and cinched the case against Dunne
当在马桶水箱里找到了凶器---一把刀
when they found the murder weapon, a knife,
也就把这起谋杀案牢牢对准Dunne了
in his bathroom toilet tank.
太棒了
That's great.
你还好吗
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
为什么不好呢  我完成了我的工作
Why wouldn't I be? I did my job.
我在紧急关头抓住了Dunne
I got Dunne off on the hit-and-run.
你做的很好
Yeah, you did it well.
是的 不管他之后发生了什么
Yes, and whatever happened to him after that,
都跟我没关系
it's not my concern.
正义终被伸张
Justice was served, all around.
好了 慢用
Okay. Here you go.
介意跟我一起吃顿饭吗
Care to join me for dinner?
肉饼和土豆泥
Hmm, meat loaf and mashed potatoes?
我的最爱 我很乐意
My favorite. I would be happy to.
马上就好
Coming right up.
谢谢 Elaine
Thanks, Elaine.
我觉得我们还是有一些共同点的
I think that you and me have a few things in common.
==GA字幕组==
翻译：入江之鲸 冰糖 一生为白 飞行猪 开心的小末
校对：流年打死不表白 关注海燕的毯子 lynhoo00 没抢到东西的蓉小张 K在苦逼找事做 伽尘师太
字幕特效/时间轴：闹不闹得住菇 无限Boss爱渣  压制：米兰伯爵
阿鲸-要认认真真地学习工作和生活~
冰糖-希望下雨的日子赶快过去吧^^
小白-纽约竟然下雪了，我要回深圳过冬
小末-小末不要mg嫁给别人
飞行猪-Tony每次都灵感爆发啊！
伯爵-我也想跟Boss一起吃土豆泥肉饼（这玩意吃不胖吗？Boss的肌肉哪里来的？）
毯子-祝贺小末末拿到奖学金！小麦和Delilah感情很稳定啊~
K-谁娶到那个旅店老婆谁倒霉
佳晨-热哭的广东终于降温了
流年-麦呆和眼镜兄还真挺八卦
lynhoo00-Gibbs和那女律师虾米关系？Tony为啥关心人家离婚没？
蓉蓉-弱弱的觉得女律师不错